<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<id>urn:uuid:71cb282f-3cdb-416c-8b0a-2d6c7d4c4207</id>
	<title>ShutdownGuard</title>
	<link href="http://shutdownguard.googlecode.com/svn/wiki/feed.xml" rel="self" />
	<link href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/" />
	<updated>2009-01-17T14:40:00Z</updated>
	<author>
		<name>Stefan Sundin</name>
		<email>recover89@gmail.com</email>
	</author>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:6ce5a803-d195-4ef2-9da7-2d344ebe2e0f</id>
		<title>ShutdownGuard - Nynorsk translation</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/" />
		<updated>2009-01-17T14:40:00Z</updated>
		<content type="text">
I got a translation for Nynorsk from Jon Stødle, so now I'm releasing an updated installer and a 7z archive for Nynorsk.
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:d5b67385-c912-4946-9558-f2f3f6215d44</id>
		<title>ShutdownGuard - 0.3</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/" />
		<updated>2008-12-25T13:37:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
I've finally released 0.3 which addresses the problems that were introduced in the Unicode versions of 0.2. In addition to that I've implemented an update checker and the ability to configure the prevention message (example: &lt;i>Do not shut this server off!&lt;/i>). The update checker will only check for updates and notify you when one is available, you will have to download and install the update manually. I've also added a translation for Lithuanian (thanks p|b!). The 7z archives of the other languages are available if you go to the downloads section (all languages are included in the installer). I've also added instructions on how to donate, read the &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/wiki/Donate">Donate page&lt;/a>. Merry Christmas everyone!
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:0f5a93b2-5c22-4641-95c2-757ee4037488</id>
		<title>Localization and installer</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/" />
		<updated>2008-11-30T13:17:00Z</updated>
		<content type="html">
I've just released a Spanish version of ShutdownGuard 0.2. Now it's easy to translate ShutdownGuard, so if you want to translate ShutdownGuard to your language, visit the &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/wiki/Localize">Localize&lt;/a> wiki page to find some easy instructions on how to do just that. Thanks to Fabrizio Ferri for translating the Spanish version!&lt;br/>
&lt;br/>
I've also released &lt;a href="http://shutdownguard.googlecode.com/files/ShutdownGuard-0.2%20%28Installer%29.exe">an installer&lt;/a> which contains both languages. Please report any problem you find.
		</content>
	</entry>

	<entry>
		<id>urn:uuid:3f7e1873-cf11-4e49-ac97-a3234a8bd7dd</id>
		<title>ShutdownGuard - 0.2</title>
		<link href="http://code.google.com/p/shutdownguard/downloads/detail?name=ShutdownGuard-0.2.7z" />
		<updated>2008-11-15T02:45:00Z</updated>
		<content type="text">
Changelog:
* Compatible with Vista.
* Reordered shutdown dialog buttons.
* Middle click on tray brings up the shutdown dialog.
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>